destination360.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy for Destination360.com

Your privacy is very important to Destination360 ("we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("policy") describes the practices that apply to our site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information.

**Simply put:**  
• we will not collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number ("Personal Information") without your knowledge and permission;   
• we will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless you have authorized us to do so;   
• we will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you.   
The remainder of this policy describes our information handling practices in detail.

**When You Are Just Visiting Us...**  
You can always visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any Personal Information. We do collect usage information ("session data"), but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use session data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the variety of searches of our site's database, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to our site. We use this information to improve our site content and ease of use.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Destination360. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Destination360 users based on your visit to Destination360 and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**When You Decide To fill out our request form ...**  
a) Personal Information  
If you decide to fill out our request form, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. We collect Personal Information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. As mentioned, this Personal Information includes things like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number.

b) Sharing of Personal Information  
Other than as explained in this policy, we will not disclose any Personal Information we collect from you to others without your permission, except in certain limited circumstances: (a) to protect the security of our site and our rights under our Terms and Conditions of Use; (b) to protect ourselves against liability; (c) in response to legal process, (d) if we believe in good faith that the law requires it; or (e) in connection with a sale of our business or company. Please note that if we receive a formal request to disclose your Personal Information in connection with a legal action, we will attempt to tell you about it at least ten (10) days before we respond to that request, if permitted by law.

c) Additional Products and Services  
We may partner with other companies to offer you additional products or services. If you sign up for any of these additional products or services, we will share your name and any other Personal Information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the products or services you have signed up for. This policy will not cover the use of your Personal Information by these other companies. We encourage you to read each other company's privacy policy before signing up for any of its products or services.

**Links...**  
Our site provides links to other sites. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. You should carefully review the privacy statements or policies on any other site that you visit because those privacy statements or policies will apply to your visit to that site and may be very different from our policy.

**Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
